[{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":20220,"timeElapsed":141495},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":17763,"timeElapsed":159264},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":14474,"timeElapsed":173745},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":34520,"timeElapsed":208270},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":26117,"timeElapsed":234392},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":19145,"timeElapsed":253543},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679088609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":10206,"timeElapsed":263755},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":10368,"timeElapsed":274129},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7162,"timeElapsed":281296},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":10791,"timeElapsed":295468},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5629,"timeElapsed":301103},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5645,"timeElapsed":306754},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":91274,"timeElapsed":398033},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679234522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11629,"timeElapsed":409668},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256022,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":21495,"timeElapsed":431168},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":14857,"timeElapsed":446030},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":13668,"timeElapsed":459702},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":16125,"timeElapsed":475830},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679308289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7600,"timeElapsed":483435},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":20334,"timeElapsed":506024},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679337138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6255,"timeElapsed":512283},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6246,"timeElapsed":518535},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679362748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":19354,"timeElapsed":537894},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679373575,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10822,"timeElapsed":548721},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679385645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":12063,"timeElapsed":560791},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11267,"timeElapsed":572066},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679405039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8114,"timeElapsed":580185},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679420271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":15228,"timeElapsed":595417},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9908,"timeElapsed":605330},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9850,"timeElapsed":617157},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679446833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4817,"timeElapsed":621978},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679451568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4732,"timeElapsed":626714},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679465522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13949,"timeElapsed":640668},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679471208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5683,"timeElapsed":646354},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679487790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":16579,"timeElapsed":662936},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679492026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4233,"timeElapsed":667172},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679503896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":11869,"timeElapsed":679042},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679510723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":6824,"timeElapsed":685869},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679527174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14503,"timeElapsed":702320},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":33794,"timeElapsed":736117},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679565906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4932,"timeElapsed":741052},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679573628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":7717,"timeElapsed":748774},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679580870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7237,"timeElapsed":756016},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679590705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":9830,"timeElapsed":765851},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679594807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4097,"timeElapsed":769952},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679603405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":8593,"timeElapsed":778551},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679611345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7936,"timeElapsed":786491},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679622510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":8980,"timeElapsed":797656},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8110,"timeElapsed":805771},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679636617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":5988,"timeElapsed":811763},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679643024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6402,"timeElapsed":818170},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679646502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3474,"timeElapsed":821648},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679652626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6120,"timeElapsed":827772},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679661375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8744,"timeElapsed":836521},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679683719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":22338,"timeElapsed":858865},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679692745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9021,"timeElapsed":867891},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":11120,"timeElapsed":881019},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679710000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4123,"timeElapsed":885146},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679716679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6674,"timeElapsed":891825},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679724097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7414,"timeElapsed":899243},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679729968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5865,"timeElapsed":905113},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679743079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":13107,"timeElapsed":918225},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679752723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":9638,"timeElapsed":927869},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679763514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":10786,"timeElapsed":938660},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679772136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8618,"timeElapsed":947282},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679788218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":14222,"timeElapsed":963363},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679791385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3161,"timeElapsed":966531},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679798992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7603,"timeElapsed":974138},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679810170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":11173,"timeElapsed":985316},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679815959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5784,"timeElapsed":991105},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679829088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":13124,"timeElapsed":1004233},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679832774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":1007920},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679836930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4150,"timeElapsed":1012076},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679845934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":9000,"timeElapsed":1021080},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679859261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":11347,"timeElapsed":1034407},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679864181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4915,"timeElapsed":1039327},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679869472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5287,"timeElapsed":1044618},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679876580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7103,"timeElapsed":1051726},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679881606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5021,"timeElapsed":1056751},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679888225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":6615,"timeElapsed":1063371},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679892913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4684,"timeElapsed":1068059},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679900302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7386,"timeElapsed":1075448},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679905671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5365,"timeElapsed":1080817},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679917367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10048,"timeElapsed":1092513},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679922935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5564,"timeElapsed":1098081},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679930666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":7725,"timeElapsed":1105812},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679985319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":54649,"timeElapsed":1160465},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679989319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3996,"timeElapsed":1164465},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680000731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":11408,"timeElapsed":1175877},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680011099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10364,"timeElapsed":1186245},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680018267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7163,"timeElapsed":1193413},{"subjectID":"m1ebbcdx80","prolificID":"669a55b24cc0b2f6d22e5770","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b30848ce40bd2f92b3f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680026339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":8069,"timeElapsed":1201485}]